Well, that thing's clearly in the way.
이 녀석이 길을 막고 있었군
All right.
어디 보자
Damn fridge!
망할 냉장고
- 조이, 별일 없니?
- 그럼
-Hi, Joey. How you doing?
-Great...
roomie.
룸메이트
-I guess we are roommates.
-I know.
그래, 지금은 룸메이트지
그렇지, 말이 나왔으니 얘긴데
Now that you bring it up,
our fridge is broken.
우리 냉장고가 맛이 가서
새 걸 사야겠어
We need a new one.
넌 반만 내라
400달러, 고마워
I checked and your half is $400.
Thanks a lot.
뭐? 내가 왜 그 돈을 내?
I'm not paying for that.
I'm just here while they fix my place.
우리 아파트 수리되면
곧 돌아갈 건데
레이첼, 내가 태어나자마자
부모님께서 사신 냉장고야
Look, Rach, my parents bought this
fridge just after I was born. Okay?
I have never had a problem with it.
Then you show up and it breaks!
한 번도 고장이 없었는데
네가 오자마자 저 꼴이야
What does that tell you?
짚이는 거 없냐?
That refrigerators don't live
as long as people?
냉장고는 사람보다
수명이 짧다?
현금인출기는
300달러가 한도니까
You know the ATM
only lets you take out 300, so...
I'll take a check for the rest.
나머지 100달러는
수표로 받아줄게
You're joking, right?
농담도 심하시네
Of course I'm joking.
I don't take checks.
물론 농담이지
난 수표 안 받아
Thank God, you're pretty.
참 귀엽게 논다
The One With Joey's Fridge
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Hi! Do you guys know any cute guys?
혹시 괜찮은 남자 하나 없을까?
물론 있지, 내 친구 조이
Of course.
My good friend Joey over here.
오, 미안
I'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
고맙다, 챈들러
금주에 자선무도회가 있는데
랄프 로렌도 참석해서
There's a charity ball
and Ralph Lauren has a table...
나도 가야 할까봐
so I have to go.
무슨 자선행사야?
-What charity?
-I don't know.
글쎄, 나무라든가
무슨 병이라든가...
Something, either trees or disease...
Ralph mumbles a lot.
랄프가 좀 궁시렁거리잖니
네가 안 들을 때 중얼거렸어?
-He mumbles when you're not attentive?
-Yeah. It's weird.
그래, 이상하지?
But I need to find a date.
아무튼 파트너가 필요해
What kind of date?
어떤 남자를 찾는데?
자기 턱시도가 있든지
빌릴 능력이 있는 남자
Someone that has his own tux
or the ability to rent a tux.
그럼 최소한 50달러는
가진 남자라야 되겠네
So he has to be a male
who has at least $50.
우, 아슬아슬했다
So close.
-Hey, everybody!
-Hi, there.
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
- 이쪽은 엘리자베스야
- 반가워요
-This is Elizabeth.
-Hi, Elizabeth.
제가 그 학생이에요
I'm the student.
너무 귀엽다
Isn't she cute? Nope.
취소
괜한 참견 같지만
Weren't you guys supposed to...
함께 있는 거 눈에 띄면
곤란한 거 아냐?
not be seen together?
We aren't.
함께 온 거 아니에요
그럼, 이 커피하우스에서
우연히 마주친 것뿐이지
We just happen
to have run into each other here.
This is...
머리들은 참 좋아
Oh, sly!
아쉽지만 전 이만
가봐야겠어요
I wanted to meet you guys,
but I have to run.
- 또 봐요
- 그래요
-See you later?
-Okay.
-Bye, Ross.
-Bye. See you.
- 갈게요
- 안녕
-Didn't mean to run into you, sir.
-That's quite all right, ma'am.
부딪혀서 죄송해요, 교수님
뭐 괜찮습니다, 아가씨
Bye.
잘 가
왜 벌써 가지?
혹시 숙제가 많이 밀렸나?
Why is she leaving? Is it a
school night and she has homework?
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper
is due tomorrow.
그래, 분자역학 리포트가
내일까지거든
잘하라고 전해 줘
Tell her good luck with that.
다른 사람은?
한번 들어보자
Anyone else? Bring them on.
-When's her birthday?
-I don't know. Why?
쟤 생일은 언제야?
잘 모르겠다, 왜?
It's just been so long
since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
게임방 피자가게에
가본 지 너무 오래됐거든
- 난 엘리자베스 좋아
- 고맙다
-I like Elizabeth.
-Well, thanks.
걔 너무 좋으니까 올해는
쿠키 빨리 팔러 오라고 해
I like her so much, tell her
I want my cookies early this year.
A box of Thin Mints
and some Tagalongs.
'씬 민트' 한 상자랑
'태그얼롱'이면 좋아
다들 그만 놀려라
어떻게 잘돼 가냐?
Give him a break.
Ross, how's it going with her?
It's been great.
아주 좋아
She's 20, so she's not too serious,
which is perfect for me now.
20살이라 그런지 심각하지도
않고 지금 나한테는 딱이야
잘됐네, 정말 좋은 애 같아
That's great.
Seriously, she seems nice.
고맙다, 너희들이
날 짓궂게 놀려도
I know you guys like
to give me a hard time...
속마음은 그렇지
않다는 거 잘 알아
but it means a lot to me.
- 너흰 내 편이니까...
- 나도 하나 생각났다
-Just knowing..
-Okay, I got a good one.
대체 몇 살이야? 12살?
What is she, like, 12?
챈들러, 우리 관계에 대해
좀더 얘기를 해볼까?
Chandler, do we talk about
our relationship enough?
그래, 과일말이 좀 있어?
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll-Ups?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Okay.
내가 레이첼한테
딱 맞는 남자를 찾아냈어
I thought of the perfect guy
for Rachel to take to her thing.
그거 참, 우리도 찾았는데
That's so funny.
We found someone too.
그럼 레이첼이 고르면 되겠다
내 남자와 너희 폭탄 중에서
Good. She'll have a choice
between my guy and your weirdo.
왜 우리 남자가 폭탄이야?
-Why would our guy be a weirdo?
-Because that's just your taste.
너희들 취향이니까
See, Rachel's not gonna pick
your stupid guy.
레이첼은 그 바보를
고를 리가 없어
- 그래?
- 그럼
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
이 남자는 변호사야
자원봉사도 하고
My guy is a lawyer,
who does volunteer work.
게다가 이것도 있어
And he has one of these.
A face ass?
얼굴 엉덩이?
A chin dimple.
턱 보조개
Well, you know, our guy works
with Chandler.
이 남자는 챈들러 직장동료인데
착하고 똑똑하고 옷도 잘 입어
He's really nice and smart,
and he's a great dresser.
-Have you seen your guy's body?
-No. Our guy's just a floating head.
그 사람 몸 봤니?
아니, 몸은 없이 얼굴만
떠다니는 친구라서
Well, my guy is spectacular.
He's a massage client.
이 사람은 체격이 근사해
내 마사지 손님이거든
한번은 테이블에 누워있는데
내가 봤잖아, 깡그리 다
And one time, when he was on the
table, I looked at it. And I mean all of it.
-You're not supposed to look.
-Like there are police for that.
- 보면 안 되잖아
- 무슨 법이라도 있니?
그걸 봤어? 나도 너한테
마사지 받았잖아
You look? You massaged me.
I know.
그러게
Fine. Your guy may have a great body,
but our guy is really funny.
좋아, 체격이야 모르겠지만
이 남자는 정말 재미있어
챈들러처럼?
Chandler funny?
-Our guy's a great dancer.
-My guy's well-read.
- 우리 남자는 춤을 잘 춰
- 내 남자는 유식해
- 우리 남자는 머릿결이 좋아
- 내 남자는 치아가 예뻐
-Our guy has great hair.
-My guy has great teeth.
우리 남자는 냄새가 끝내 줘
Our guy smells incredible.
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
우리 남자 네 남자로
만들고 싶니?
- 야
- 그래
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
너 상태가 별로
안 좋아 보인다
The fridge broke,
so I had to eat everything.
냉장고가 고장나서
몽땅 먹어치웠어
냉동육, 아이스크림, 라임...
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
야, 갈색 병에 든 게 뭐지?
What was in that brown jar?
- 그게 아직 남았냐?
- 이젠 없어
-That's still in there?
-Not anymore.
그건 그렇고...
So anyway, how do you want to pay me?
돈은 어떻게 줄래?
Is this a service you're providing me?
날 위해 먹어줬다 이거냐?
No, for my new fridge.
For our new fridge.
아냐, 우리 냉장고를
새로 사야 되니까
Our new fridge?
우리 냉장고?
난 이제 여기 안 살아
-I don't live here anymore.
-So what?
그래서?
Look, okay, suppose we were
a divorced couple.
잘 들어, 우리가 이혼한
부부라고 생각해봐
And I got custody of the kid. Right?
아이는 내가 맡아 키웠고
그런데 아이가 죽었으면
새 아이를 사야 되잖아
Now suppose the kid dies
and I gotta buy a new kid.
그래...
Okay.
Give me $400!
400달러 내놔
참 귀엽게 논다
Thank God, you're pretty.
Professor Geller?
겔러 교수님?
Oh, a student I don't know.
오, 내가 모르는 학생인 걸?
I was wondering if I
could talk to you for a moment?
잠깐 드릴 말씀이 있어요
좋아요, 무슨 얘기죠?
Yes, of course.
What would this be regarding?
교수님 방에서 놀아요
Making out in your office.
좋지, 안으로 들어갈까?
Of course. Why don't we go inside.
-What?
-Doorknob.
- 왜요?
- 문손잡이가...
죄송해요
Sorry.
I actually do need to talk to you.
진짜 할말이 있어요
그래, 무슨 얘긴데?
What about?
봄방학이요
-Spring vacation?
봄방학이라...
Yeah, we have time off, and
a lot of people are going on trips..
네, 이번에 다들
여행을 가는데...
겔러 교수님
-Professor Geller.
-Yes, Professor Friesenstinlender.
네, 프리슨스틴렌더 교수님
I'll be with you in one moment.
잠깐만 실례할게요
So I will take one box
of the Thin Mints.
난 '씬 민트' 한 박스만
갖다줘요
모르겠어? 엘리자베스가
함께 여행을 가자는 거야
You don't understand. Elizabeth was
about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
너무 이르잖아
Is that taking it slow?
I'm not ready for this.
난 아직 준비가 안 됐어
뭐라고 얘기하지?
-What do I tell her?
-Tell her the truth, tell her you're not ready.
사실대로 말해
준비가 안 됐다고
I could do that.
그럼 되겠구나
-What if she gets upset?
-Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
화내면 어쩌지?
바비 인형으로 달래
아니면...
Or you could just, you know, you...
이렇게 해봐
이게 무슨 짓이야?
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell am I doing?
You just broke my fridge!
무슨 짓이라니
냉장고 고장났잖아
What? How do..?
뭐? 보지도 않고
고장 난 건 어떻게 알아
How do you know it's even broken?
내가 냉장고 고장 난 것도
모를 것 같냐?
You think I don't know
what breaks my fridge?
볼까?
Excuse me!
그럼 그렇지
Well, what do you know?
맛 갔어
Broken!
400달러 되겠수다
That'll be $400.
Joey, I saw you push him.
조이, 네가 미는 거 봤어
네가 밀었잖아
You pushed him.
Joey, I did not break this. Okay?
That has been broken for a while.
내가 고장 낸 거 아냐
고장 난 지 한참 됐다
전에 내가 냉장고 얘기했지?
Remember I told you about our fridge?
I still haven't gotten the check
for your half yet.
절반을 아직 못 받았는데?
Do not give him any money!
한 푼도 주지 마
끼어들지 마
냉장고 파괴범아
I'm not talking to you!
You broke my fridge!
절 찾으셨나요, 교수님?
-You wanted to see me, Professor Geller?
-Yes. Please come in.
네, 그래요
들어오세요
또 손잡이예요?
-Doorknob?
-Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
그래, 얘가 널 좋아하나 봐
I wanted to finish
talking to you about spring vacation.
그 봄방학 얘기를
마저 끝내고 싶어서
Good.
좋아요
Look, I...
저기, 난..
Look, I'm having
a great time with you.
난 너를 좋아하지만
진전이 너무 빨라
And I just don't want us to move too
fast or put too much pressure on us.
부담 느끼는 것도 싫고
So I'm sorry, I just don't think
we should go away together yet.
미안하지만 이번 여행은 함께
못 가겠어, 너무 이른 것 같아
It's too soon.
Ross, I think you misunderstood
what I was saying.
교수님, 제 말을 오해하셨군요
I just wanted to tell you that I'm
going to Florida for a couple weeks.
잠시 플로리다에 다녀온다는
말씀을 드리려고 한 것뿐인데
No.
아니
I think you misunderstood
what I was saying.
너야말로 내 얘기를 오해했구나
What I meant was..
- 그러니까 내 얘기는...
- 너무 귀여워요
You are so adorable.
That. Let's talk about that.
맞아
그 얘기를 해보자
-Hi.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
엘리자베스는 어떻게 됐어?
How did it go with Elizabeth?
별일 아냐
내가 오해했었나 봐
Fine. Just a misunderstanding.
She didn't want me to go with her.
나랑 가자는 얘기가 아니라
She just wanted to let me know
she's going to Florida for a spring vacation.
봄방학 동안 플로리다에
다녀온다는 뜻이었어
단순한 봄방학이라기보다
봄 휴가 아닐까? 헬렐레!
Wait a minute. Is she going
for spring vacation or spring break? Wahoo!
What's the difference?
차이점이 뭔데?
봄방학은 할아버지 할머니랑
조신하게 지내는 거고
Spring vacation, you're doing nice things
with your grandparents.
봄 휴가는 좀 노는 거지
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
You know what?
Not all spring breaks are like that.
봄 휴가라고 다 그렇진 않아
넌 어땠는데?
-What did you do on yours?
-I went to Egypt with my dad.
아빠랑 이집트에 갔었어
I can see it now.
"Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx, wahoo!"
안 봐도 훤하다
'아빠, 스핑크스예요, 헬렐레! '
I think Elizabeth is a little more
serious than: "Spring break, wahoo!"
엘리자베스는 이러지 않아
'봄 휴가다, 헬렐레! '
Come on, she's taking my class.
- 내 강의를 듣는 애야
- 교수랑 잠도 자고
-And slept with the professor.
-I'm gonna call her.
- 전화해야겠다
- 그래라
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
You guys,
I want you to meet Sebastian.
세바스찬을 소개할게
안녕하세요?
We met at the newsstand. We both
grabbed for the last Field and Stream.
방금 가판대에서 만났는데
이 잡지를 동시에 집었지 뭐야?
What? I read that.
왜? 나 이거 읽어
-Can I get you a cup of coffee?
-Yes. Thank you.
- 커피 드실래요?
- 네, 고마워요
이게 무슨 짓이야?
-Rachel, what the hell is this?
-What?
뭐?
남자 하나 구해달라더니
직접 끌고 나타났잖아
You ask us to find a guy, and you come
traipsing in here with a guy of your own?
찾았니?
You found me a guy?
그래, 챈들러 직장동료인데
진짜 멋있고 재미있는 남자야
Yes. We found you a really cute,
funny guy from Chandler's work.
Yeah, and I found you one too,
who is not a weirdo.
나도 한 명 찾았는데
폭탄 절대 아냐
You know what though, guys,
I really appreciate that...
생각해준 건 정말 고마운데
난 세바스찬이랑 갈 거야
but I'm gonna take Sebastian.
Are you sure?
Our guy smells incredible.
정말이야? 이 친구는
냄새가 끝내주는데
Would you stop it with that already?
그 얘기 좀 닥쳐줄래?
여기 있어요
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
- 고마워요
- 뭘요
So, Sebastian,
do you do any volunteer work?
세바스찬, 그쪽은
자원봉사 하세요?
아뇨, 왜 그러시죠?
-Not really. Why?
-No reason.
그냥 남을 위해 일하는
독신남을 하나 알거든요
I know a single guy
who does care about other people.
선생 웃기쇼?
Are you funny?
-Excuse me?
-What are you guys doing?
뭐라고요?
너희들 지금 뭐 하자는 거니?
웃길 줄 알아요?
조크 하나 해보쇼!
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
I just wanted to have coffee
with Rachel.
레이첼이랑 커피 한잔
하고 싶었을 뿐이에요
다들 그러죠
Well, so do a lot of people.
전 이만 가볼게요
-Actually, I gotta get going.
-But you..
- 그래도...
- 나중에 전화해요
-Give me a call sometime.
-You didn't give me your phone number.
전화번호 안 주셨잖아요
네, 다음에 봅시다
Okay, see you later.
Turns out he is kind of funny.
재미는 좀 있네
이래도 되는 거야?
I cannot believe you guys!
정말 괜찮은 사람인데
너희들 때문에 가버렸어
He was really nice,
and he just left because of you!
다 좋은데 세바스찬?
무슨 고양이 이름이냐?
Yeah, but "Sebastian"?
What is that, a cat's name?
You know what I noticed, Rachel?
He scares easy.
다른 건 모르겠지만
겁이 너무 많다 얘
저런 사람이랑 무도회에 가봐
Is that the kind of guy you wanna take
to a ball?
'세바스찬, 우리 춤출까요?'
"Hey, Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
'네, 전 이만 갈게요'
"Okay. I gotta go."
다들 그만하자
Stop it.
Rachel, we're very sorry.
레이첼, 미안하다
우리가 너무 심했어
That is a very
insensitive thing to do.
하지만 정말 괜찮은 남자를
두 명 구해놨으니까 만나봐
Let us make it up to you.
We have two really great guys for you.
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
그래, 손해 볼 거 없잖아
좋은 인연이 될지도 몰라
You might even end up with someone
really special. If you pick my guy.
내 남자를 고르면
-All right.
-So you will meet our guys?
알았다
그럼 우리가 고른 남자 만날래?
Yes.
그래, 만날게
누굴 고르든 전적으로
네 판단에 달렸어
It doesn't matter which one you choose.
It's up to you.
Our guy is perfect.
우리 남자는 완벽해
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe
deemed not good enough for herself.
아니면 피비가 갖기 싫은
남자를 선택해도 좋고
피비, 너 우리 냉장고
고장냈으니까 400달러 내놔
There you are!
You broke my fridge.
You owe me $400.
-Okay, sure.
-Really?
- 그래, 알았어
- 진짜?
Technically, you owe me $600
for sending out happy thoughts...
정확히 계산하자면
오디션 볼 때마다 내가 희망을
심어줬으니까 넌 600달러 내놔
on your last 10 auditions.
Call it even?
비긴 걸로 할까?
Okay.
좋아
There you are.
왔구나
엘리자베스가 뭐래?
What did Elizabeth say?
Turns out she is going to Daytona
for "spring break, wahoo."
데이토너로 갈 거래
봄 휴가, 헬렐레야
젖은 티셔츠 콘테스트에
사내놈들은 발광을 하고
That means wet T-shirt contests, guys
doing shots off of girls' bodies...
낯선 사람 옆에서 잠을 깨겠지
waking up with strangers.
She is gonna have a great time!
진짜 뻑적지근하게 놀겠다
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
코로나 호텔에 묵는대?
그 호텔 아냐?
-You know the hotels?
-I was there! Spring Break '81, wahoo!
물론이지
81년 봄 휴가, 헬렐레!
In 1981, you were 13.
1981이면 넌 13살이었어
그게 뭐, 차 끌고 가서
티셔츠를 팔았잖아
So? I drove down, sold T-shirts.
Had a blast.
You know who knows how to party?
Drunk college chicks.
파티 하면 누군 줄 알아?
술에 떡이 된 여대생들
Okay, she can't go.
그럼 도저히 못 보내지
You can't tell her not to go.
You just started dating.
사귄 지 얼마나 됐다고
이래라저래라 하니
- 그럼 어떡하라고?
- 놔두고 가만히 지켜봐
-What am I supposed to do?
-You just have to be cool with it.
거기 가서
아무 남자랑 막 자도?
What if she goes down there and sleeps
with a bunch of guys?
그럼 이번엔 결혼하지 마라
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
미안, 웃을 일이 아닌데
너무 걱정하지 마
I'm sorry, this is very serious.
And you know what, Ross?
서로를 좋아하니까
다 잘 풀릴 거야
You like her, she likes you,
everything's gonna be fine.
맞아, 이건 지나친 반응이야
You're right.
I'm probably overreacting.
수영장 딸린 해변 호텔에서
먹고 마시며 쉬는 것뿐인데
It's just she's staying at this party hotel
on the beach...
with a huge pool and free drinks
with every meal.
그런 능력이면 자기가 고장 낸
냉장고 값도 낼 수 있겠네
If she's got enough money for that, she
can certainly pat for the fridge she broke.
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.
떠난다니 너무 기뻐
네, 이번 학기엔
너무 힘들었어요
I've been working
so hard this semester.
모든 걸 다 잊고
긴장을 풀고 싶어요
I really need to go crazy,
blow off some steam.
Sure.
좋지, 아무렴
물론 마음을 굳힌 건 알지만
Look, I don't know if your plans
are finalized yet, but...
긴장을 풀고 싶다면
다른 방법도 있어
I know a great way
to blow off steam.
-What?
-Are you into crafts at all?
뭔데요?
혹시 수공예에 관심 있어?
Ross, are you okay?
교수님 괜찮아요?
물론 난 괜찮아
도움을 주려는 거야
Yeah. Of course I'm okay.
I'm just being supportive.
난 네 편이니까
떠나는 것도 찬성이야
Supportive of you
and this whole trip...
and what's this?
근데 이건...
대체 뭘까요?
수영복이에요
It's a bathing suit?
사람들 앞에서 입는 거?
To wear in front of people?
Is that supportive?
- 그게 도와주는 거예요?
- 이건 도움이 되나?
Is this?
- 안녕?
- 그래, 좋아
Okay, good.
- 우리 왔어
- 그래
-Hey.
-Hi.
그 사람 만나보겠다니
정말 잘 생각했다
We're so glad you decided to
meet our guy. You'll like him so much.
맘에 들 거야
언제 만날래?
-When do you want to meet him?
-I don't know.
글쎄, 내일은 일찍 퇴근해
-I don't work late tomorrow night.
-Tomorrow night is good.
내일 밤도 좋긴 한데
그때까지 미룰 거 뭐 있어?
But why put off something till
tomorrow that you could do it right now?
당장 해치울 수 있는데
엘다드, 이리 와
-Eldad, come here!
-What?
- 엘다드, 레이첼이에요
- 안녕하세요?
-This is Rachel.
-How are you?
A little blindsided but good.
자세히는 안 보이지만 괜찮네요
Eldad, sit down. Move over now.
엘다드, 앉아
뭐해, 저쪽으로 가
There you go. There you are.
자, 여기 앉으라고
좋아, 우린 빠져주자
Okay, we can take a hint!
What? What are you doing here?
너 여기서 뭐해?
This is Patrick.
여긴 패트릭이야
- 안녕하세요?
- 반가워요
-Hi.
너무 늦으셨구만
이미 우리 남자를 만났어
You're too late because
she's already with our guy.
맙소사, 정말 늦었네
둘이 앉아서 얘기씩이나?
You're right, I am too late.
They're sitting on the couch and talking.
Come on.
이리 와요
- 레이첼?
- 응?
Rachel? This is Patrick.
이쪽은 패트릭이야
- 안녕하세요?
- 반갑습니다
-Hi.
This is the guy I was telling you about.
내가 말한 사람이야
이 옷 속엔 엄청난 몸매가
숨겨져 있다는 걸 알아둬
This suit does not do justice
to what's underneath it.
Okay.
알았어
But, Phoebe, I'm just sort of
in the middle of something.
- 잠깐만
- 그래
난 지금 볼일이 있어
그렇지, 괜찮아
여기 앉아요
Okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
-You can't do that!
-I should go.
- 그럼 안 되지
- 전 이만 가보죠
이기고 있는데 왜 이래요
Sit down, we're winning.
Maybe I should go.
내가 가야겠다
- 안 돼, 앉아있어
- 그러지 마
No. Have a seat!
레이첼, 아직 엘다드의
머리를 안 만져봤잖아
Rachel, you haven't touched
Eldad's hair.
-He has the softest hair. Touch it.
-I'm good.
얼마나 부드러운데, 만져봐
됐어
레이첼, 패트릭은 부자야
쟤한테 돈 좀 주세요
Rachel, Patrick is really rich.
Give her some money.
This isn't really worth the free massage.
공짜 마사지 한 번에
이건 좀 심하잖아요
맞아요, 패트릭
잘 가요
-That's right. Bye-bye.
-No.
엘다드가 훨씬 협조적이고
춤도 잘 추지
Eldad is much more cooperative,
and he can dance.
You dance for Rachel.
한번 보여드려
아니, 제발 하지 말아요
Don't dance for me. Please!
너희들 진짜 왜 이래
What is the matter with you?
그래, 얘기 좀 해보자
Yeah, let's talk it out.
너흰 창피하지도 않아?
Am I the only one that this is
embarrassing for?
I'm a little embarrassed.
난 좀 창피하군요
I'll tell you who should
be embarrassed. It's you guys.
진짜 부끄러운 짓을
한 건 너희들이야
정말 웃기지도 않아
고맙지만 이제 남자는 됐어
I do not need you
to get me a date.
- 그럼 왜 전에는..
- 내 얘기 안 끝났어
-Why did she ask us to..?
-I am still talking!
내 맘에 드는 남자는
쫓아버리고
Then you chase away
the one guy I actually liked.
두 분한테는 감정 없어요
돈 많아서 좋으시겠어요
No offense to you guys.
Really, congratulations on...
all the cash.
그리고 머릿결 진짜 부드럽네요
And you really do have very soft hair.
But I'd much rather go to the ball by
myself than go through any more of this.
이런 바보짓을 계속하느니
차라리 혼자 가겠어, 잘 있어
Goodbye.
Now, do you use some sort of
special conditioner on that hair?
샴푸 어떤 거 써요?
Papaya extract.
- 파파야 추출물이요
- 고마워요
Thank you.
So have a great time down there.
그럼 즐겁게 놀다 와
-I will.
-Yeah.
- 알았어요
- 그래
- 참, 그 수영복도 쌌어?
- 네
-Did you pack that bathing suit?
-Yeah.
내가 잠깐 숨겨둬서
재미있었지?
It was pretty funny
when I hid it for a while.
어쨌든, 음...
Anyway.
그 수영복이 문제가 되는 건
노출이 심해서가 절대 아니고
I am worried about that suit.
Not because it's revealing,
which I'm fine with.
네 건강이 걱정돼서 그래
I'm concerned about your health.
자외선이 강하니까
Sun exposure.
Don't worry, I have plenty of sun block.
걱정 마세요
차단제 있으니까
SPF-30이에요
-It's SPF 30.
-All right.
사실 병에 든 게
30이라 하더라도
Well, if what's in the bottle
is actually 30.
Sometimes you get 30,
sometimes it's 4 and...
가끔은 4정도밖에 안 된대
장담하건데 그건
우유나 진배없어
more often than not, it's just milk.
로스, 염려 말아요
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
남자들 만나러 가는 거 아니에요
I'm not going down there
to hook up with a bunch of guys.
교수님이 정말 좋아요
I really like you.
- 함께 있으면 행복하니까
- 정말?
I like how things are going between us.
-Really?
-Yeah.
네, 친구들이랑
좀 쉬고 오는 거예요
I'm just going down there to relax
and hang out with my friends.
그래, 좋아
Okay. Cool.
Here they are!
네, 저기 왔네요
엘리자베스!
전화해!
Call me!
Sorry for pushing those guys on you.
우리가 못할 짓을 한 것 같다
괜찮아, 정말 즐거운 파티였어
That's all right.
I ended up having a really good time.
자선행사도 잘 풀려서
돈이 많이 모였거든
The charity was a big success, and they
raised a lot of money and awareness.
근데 무슨 행사였어?
So, what was it for anyway?
아마 질병이겠지
I wanna say a disease.
- 얘들아
- 그래
로스가 이상한 메시지를 보냈어
MTV를 틀어보라는 거야
I just got this really weird message
from Ross. He said to turn on MTV.
됐다
세상에, 엘리자베스야
Oh, my God, look! That's Elizabeth!
오, 겔러 교수님
Professor Geller.
13살 시절이 그립다
To be 13 again....